# **Dawud Saiyed Rehan**

GitHub: https://github.com/drehan7

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dawud-rehan-222624198/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/dawud-rehan-222624198/</a>

#### SKILLS

Creating responsive web pages using Django Framework with Python including Javascript, HTML, and CSS. Using Postgres and SQL to manipulate and keep track of data. Working in Agile teams to develop responsive web-pages using version control and collaboration via Git/Github.

Experience writing and utilizing APIs. (Django Rest Framework)

Using React JS Framework to connect to APIs and display data dynamically

Team-building, management, and communication.

Coursera Python Specialization

Knowledge in Object-Oriented Programming

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Momentum, Remote - Software Engineer

Jan 2021 - PRESENT

- 16 week full-stack software development bootcamp with a curriculum based on real-world applications.
- Worked remotely with teammates to develop clean, responsive web applications.
- Strengthened skills in different technologies: Python, ReactJS, SQL, Git, Heroku.

## Tazza Kitchen, Cary NC - Assistant Kitchen Manager

Jan 2018 - Sep 2020

- Supervised daily operations of the kitchen.
- Took weekly inventory and daily orders while maintaining optimal finances
- Conducted training and reviews for staff.

## **EDUCATION**

## Wake Tech/NC State, Raleigh NC -

Aug 2015 - Jul 2018

Credits for CS Major